<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cheezy World</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Cheezy World</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 09:52:02 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Building a LiveView app using AI - Part 1</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/ai-kanban-part1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 09:52:02 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/ai-kanban-part1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;getting-started&#34;&gt;Getting Started&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is the first post in a series in which I will be building a Kanban board application using Phoenix and LiveView. I will be using AI to help me build the application. I will be sharing the tools I use, the workflow that works best for me, and the results.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This post lays down the foundation of what tools I will be using and what things I will add to my application in order to make my LLM more effective.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 12:41:47 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;about-me&#34;&gt;About Me&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Hello, I&amp;rsquo;m Jeff &amp;ldquo;Cheezy&amp;rdquo; Morgan and yes Cheezy is a nickname given to me a long time ago. I have worked with development teams and leadership for over 30 years. This blog is where I share ideas and experiences I have working with modern tools, exploring AI and machine learning, and rapid delivery techniques while delivering software for my clients and building my own applications.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hello world (again eh)!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/hello-world-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 07:43:32 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/hello-world-again/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;im-back&#34;&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m back&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It has been a while since I&amp;rsquo;ve blogged. I had a blog named CheezyWorld.com&#xA;for many years but stopped posting more than 12 years ago. At the time I was traveling for work as well as traveling around the world to speak at conferences. My life circumstances are different now and I am happy to return to blogging. I am doing (and have been doing) a lot of exciting work and have a lot to share.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
