<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cheezy World</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Cheezy World</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 15:13:21 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Building a LiveView app using AI - Part 5</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/ai-kanban-part5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Oct 2025 15:13:21 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/ai-kanban-part5/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;follow-up-for-the-french-translations&#34;&gt;Follow up for the French Translations&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;After the last recording I started manually looking at the translatons. I quickly noticed that the authentication pages were not translated. This is why I take very small steps and verify after each one. LLMs cannot read your mind and they do not always do what you think they should do. Small steps allow us to make adjustments or revert when this happens. I asked Claude to translate them and it did.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building a LiveView app using AI - Part 4</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/ai-kanban-part4/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 10:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/ai-kanban-part4/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;taking-a-detour&#34;&gt;Taking a Detour&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I decided to change the plan a little and take care of a couple of user facing issues. Let&amp;rsquo;s see how that goes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;&#xA;      &lt;iframe allow=&#34;accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share; fullscreen&#34; loading=&#34;eager&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;strict-origin-when-cross-origin&#34; src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/uRwOkTFssaA?autoplay=0&amp;amp;controls=1&amp;amp;end=0&amp;amp;loop=0&amp;amp;mute=0&amp;amp;start=0&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; title=&#34;YouTube video&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So we have a new plan. I will be making the site pretty (and responsive) and I will be adding internationalization including the French language support for all existing pages. Should I trust Claude to come up with my design? What should I expect out of an LLM? Let&amp;rsquo;s see the results of the first part of this revised plan.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building a LiveView app using AI - Part 3</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/ai-kanban-part3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 11:18:02 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/ai-kanban-part3/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;using-claude-code-to-write-the-authentication-code&#34;&gt;Using Claude Code to write the Authentication Code&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In Part 3 of this series we are finally ready to allow Claude Code to wite some code. We have our system configured properly, we have created a plan to take small steps, and now it is time to get started. I will be using Claude Code to build the Authentication for our Kanban Board application. There are a few times where I had to ask Claude to do something different. It is always important to pay attention. After the video was complete It took the time to verify everything and look at the code. Everything was good as I expected.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building a LiveView app using AI - Part 2</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/ai-kanban-part2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 09:52:02 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/ai-kanban-part2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;using-claude-code-to-create-the-plan&#34;&gt;Using Claude Code to create the plan&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In Part 2 of this series I will be using Claude Code to generate a plan to build the Kanban Board application. It is very important to me that the plan take very small steps and include a lot of places where we check the quality along the way. Here is a video of the session.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;&#xA;      &lt;iframe allow=&#34;accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share; fullscreen&#34; loading=&#34;eager&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;strict-origin-when-cross-origin&#34; src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/nipOWuKmI8Q?autoplay=0&amp;amp;controls=1&amp;amp;end=0&amp;amp;loop=0&amp;amp;mute=0&amp;amp;start=0&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; title=&#34;YouTube video&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;the-plan&#34;&gt;The Plan&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;So you can see what Claude Code produced, I am including the entire plan here.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TDD With AI</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/tdd-with-ai/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 09:52:02 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/tdd-with-ai/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;im-a-tdd-guy&#34;&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m a TDD guy&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I have been writing code using Test Driven Development for about 25 years. I am a huge believer in the benefits of this practice. I have spoken about it at conferences around the world and have taught many workshops on the subject. As I started to dig into AI the first thing I tried to do is see how it would fit into my TDD workflow. I tried numerous approaches and they all felt unnatural. I watched videos of others try to do the same and didn&amp;rsquo;t feel like they were successful.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building a LiveView app using AI - Part 1</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/ai-kanban-part1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 09:52:02 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/ai-kanban-part1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;getting-started&#34;&gt;Getting Started&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is the first post in a series in which I will be building a Kanban board application with &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.phoenixframework.org&#34;&gt;Phoenix&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://hexdocs.pm/phoenix_live_view/Phoenix.LiveView.html&#34;&gt;LiveView&lt;/a&gt;. What is different about this series is that I will use AI to write the code and tests as well as come up with the design of the application.  I will be using a set of tools and workflow that I have worked out over the past several months to truly take advantage of the benefits of AI while producing quality code and a fully tested application.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 12:41:47 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;about-me&#34;&gt;About Me&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Hello, I&amp;rsquo;m Jeff &amp;ldquo;Cheezy&amp;rdquo; Morgan and yes Cheezy is a nickname given to me a long time ago. I have worked with development teams and leadership for over 30 years. This blog is where I share ideas and experiences I have working with modern tools, exploring AI and machine learning, and rapid delivery techniques while delivering software for my clients and building my own applications.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hello world (again eh)!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/hello-world-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 07:43:32 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/hello-world-again/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;im-back&#34;&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m back&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It has been a while since I&amp;rsquo;ve blogged. I had a blog named CheezyWorld.com&#xA;for many years but stopped posting more than 12 years ago. At the time I was traveling for work as well as traveling around the world to speak at conferences. My life circumstances are different now and I am happy to return to blogging. I am doing (and have been doing) a lot of exciting work and have a lot to share.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
