<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cheezy World</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Cheezy World</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 09:52:02 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Building a LiveView app using AI - Part 2</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/ai-kanban-part2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 09:52:02 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/ai-kanban-part2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;using-claude-code-to-create-the-plan&#34;&gt;Using Claude Code to create the plan&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In Part 2 of this series I will be using Claude Code to generate a plan to build the Kanban Board application. It is very important to me that the plan take very small steps and include a lot of places where we check the quality along the way. Here is a video of the session. Following the video I include the prompts I used as well as the entire plan created by Claude.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TDD With AI</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/tdd-with-ai/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 09:52:02 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/tdd-with-ai/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;im-a-tdd-guy&#34;&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m a TDD guy&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I have been writing code using Test Driven Development for about 25 years. I am a huge believer in the benefits of this practice. I have spoken about it at conferences around the world and have taught many workshops on the subject. As I started to dig into AI the first thing I tried to do is see how it would fit into my TDD workflow. I tried numerous approaches and they all felt unnatural. I watched videos of others try to do the same and didn&amp;rsquo;t feel like they were successful.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building a LiveView app using AI - Part 1</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/ai-kanban-part1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2025 09:52:02 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/ai-kanban-part1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;getting-started&#34;&gt;Getting Started&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This is the first post in a series in which I will be building a Kanban board application with &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.phoenixframework.org&#34;&gt;Phoenix&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://hexdocs.pm/phoenix_live_view/Phoenix.LiveView.html&#34;&gt;LiveView&lt;/a&gt;. What is different about this series is that I will use AI to write the code and tests as well as come up with the design of the application.  I will be using a set of tools and workflow that I have worked out over the past several months to truly take advantage of the benefits of AI while producing quality code and a fully tested application.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 12:41:47 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;about-me&#34;&gt;About Me&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Hello, I&amp;rsquo;m Jeff &amp;ldquo;Cheezy&amp;rdquo; Morgan and yes Cheezy is a nickname given to me a long time ago. This blog is where I share ideas and experiences I have as I work with teams delivering software and as I build my own applications. Hopefully you find some value in the things I write.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hello world (again eh)!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/hello-world-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 07:43:32 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/hello-world-again/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;im-back&#34;&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m back&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It has been a while since I&amp;rsquo;ve blogged. I had a blog named CheezyWorld.com&#xA;for many years but stopped posting more than 12 years ago. At the time I was traveling for work as well as traveling around the world to speak at conferences. My life circumstances are different now and I am happy to return to blogging. I am doing (and have been doing) a lot of exciting work and have a lot to share.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
