<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Continuous Delivery on Cheezy World</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/continuous-delivery/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Continuous Delivery on Cheezy World</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 08:32:51 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/continuous-delivery/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Stride goes full AI</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/stride-next/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 08:32:51 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/stride-next/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;building-an-ai-optimized-kanban-system-a-human-ai-collaboration-experiment&#34;&gt;Building an AI-Optimized Kanban System: A Human-AI Collaboration Experiment&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m embarking on an experiment to build a Kanban task management system specifically designed for AI-human collaboration. This isn&amp;rsquo;t just another project management tool—it&amp;rsquo;s a system where AI agents and humans work together as peers on software development tasks.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-vision&#34;&gt;The Vision&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Most task management tools treat tasks as simple items with a title and description. But when you&amp;rsquo;re working with AI agents (like Claude, GPT-4, or custom agents), they need much more context to be effective. They need to understand:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tensions with AI</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/ai-tensions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 06:38:22 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/ai-tensions/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;bringing-ai-into-your-organization&#34;&gt;Bringing AI into your organization&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I have now worked with multiple teams that have introduced an AI driven development into their development workflow and I have seen a pattern emerge. When AI, and more specifically Vibe Coding, is introduced into a traditional software development organization that are following an Agile process there are three tensions that quickly arise. All three of these tensions are due to the rapid pace of development.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hello world (again eh)!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/post/hello-world-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 07:43:32 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/hello-world-again/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;im-back&#34;&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m back&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It has been a while since I&amp;rsquo;ve blogged. I had a blog named CheezyWorld.com&#xA;for many years but stopped posting more than 12 years ago. At the time I was traveling for work as well as traveling around the world to speak at conferences. My life circumstances are different now and I am happy to return to blogging. I am doing (and have been doing) a lot of exciting work and have a lot to share.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
